http://jonessodatest.myshopify.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
PRIVACY STATEMENT
Jones Soda Co. (referred to as "Jones," "we," "us," or "our" herein) recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personal information collected from users of our Web site. This Privacy Statement discloses how we collect, use, and share information gathered about users when they visit our Web site. By accessing our Web site, you are assenting to the terms of this Privacy Statement and the terms of the user agreement, located at www.jonessoda.com/terms-of-use, including without limitation, the limitation of liability provisions. A COPY OF THE PRIVACY POLICY MAY BE DOWNLOADED, STORED OR PRINTED.
CHILDREN
Jones is committed to protecting the on-line privacy of children. While this site is not designed or intended to attract children under the age of thirteen (13), we are mindful children may also visit this site. We do not collect personal information from children we know are under 13 years of age.
If you have questions or concerns about the Internet and privacy for your child, we encourage you to check out www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
Jones collects personally identifiable information, such as name, address, and email address from numerous areas on our Web site. Below we describe the major areas on our Web site from which we collect personal information. We collect personal information in order to respond and fulfill your requests for our products and to better meet customer needs. Currently, we do not sell, share, or rent personal information collected from our users to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Statement. However, we reserve our right to do so in the future. In addition, we may share your personal information with business partners that we have contracted with to help process orders and deliver products and services that you have requested.
Registration and Promotions:
We send all new users who register a welcoming email confirming their username and password. Established members may also receive information on products or special deals ("promotional emails"). If, however, you do not want to receive promotional emails, you may indicate your preference by replying to the email, typing "unsubscribe" in the subject line, and sending it back to us. Or, you may email us directly at info@jonessoda.com and notify us that you do not want to receive promotional emails from us.
Financial Information:
When you purchase a product on our Web site, we need you to provide your name, email, address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number and credit card information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders.
Some Jones sites may offer shopping services, member services or other features which request you to provide financial information such as account or credit card numbers.
Jones Soda will use your financial information to bill you for products and services or otherwise process your transaction. By making a purchase on the Jones Soda site, you consent to our providing your financial information to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine is necessary to process your transactions. These third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process the transaction.
Contests and Promotions:
When entering a contest or other promotional feature, Jones may ask for the user's contact information (such as name, address and email address) and demographic information (such as zip code). The contact information will be used so we are able to administer the contest and promotions and to notify winners. The demographic information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the Web site. Participation in these contests and promotions is completely voluntary.
Newsletters:
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information, such as name and email address. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may indicate their preference by replying "unsubscribe" in the subject line and sending it back to us. Or, a user may email us directly at info@jonessoda.com and ask to be removed from the newsletter mailing list.
Bulletin Boards and Chat:
Jones provides bulletin boards and chat rooms for registered members of its Web site. We ask for username, passwords, email address, city and state, occupation, and Web address for those interested in participating in the bulletin boards. To participate in the chat rooms, we ask users to provide a nickname and an email address. We ask that all users of the bulletin boards and the chat rooms comply with our public forum guidelines available at www.jonessoda.com/terms-of-use.
Gallery/Labels/Photo Submissions:
Jones provides users with an opportunity to submit their ideas, photos and other artwork for display on the Web site and for possible use as a label on bottles of Jones soda. In order to submit anything, users must be registered with jonessoda.com. The submission of any items to Jones will be subject to the terms of the jonessoda.com user agreement, located at www.jonessoda.com/terms-of-use.
UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
If you would like to update your personal information, please send an email to info@jonessoda.com with your new information and a brief explanation of what information you would like to have updated. Alternatively, you may send a fax to PRIVACY OFFICER at 206-624-6857 with the information you would like changed. Please describe your changes clearly and allow five business days to process your request.
SECURITY
Jones takes precautions to protect the personal information we collect from our users. For example, sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, are collected on a Web page enhanced with secure sockets layer protocol to protect the confidentiality of the data. However, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Although we make reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, we cannot warrant the security of information you transmit to us.
COOKIES
A "cookie" is a small file stored on your computer by a Web site that gives users a numeric user identification and stores certain information about the user's activity on the Web site. We use cookies to let us know that the user is a prior customer and to provide certain features such as storage of the user's password or user name. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but most allow you to instruct your browser to prevent the use of cookies. However, if you disable this feature, certain aspects of our Web site, such as the shopping cart, will not function properly.
INTERNET PROTOCOL (IP) ADDRESSES
Jones uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Web site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.
LINKS
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other Web sites that you may link to from the Jonessoda.com Web site. We ask our users to be aware that when they enter other Web sites they will be subject to privacy practices that may differ from ours. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of each Web site that you link to and that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected on the jonessoda.com Web site.
CONSENT AND NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of personal information as described above by Jones. If we decide to change our Privacy Statement, we will post these changes so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. We encourage you to check this page from time to time because your continued use of this Web site following any changes to the Privacy Policy will be deemed to constitute your acceptance of such changes.
FEEDBACK
Jones welcomes your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to this, or any other issue to info@jonessoda.com.
Run with the little guy... create some change.
